const STORE = [
  {
		question: 'One of the first African-American to ever receive her Ph.D. in mathematics, this woman performed pioneering work in the field of computing.',
		answer: 'Evelyn Boyd Granville',
		choices: ['Jean Bartik', 'Sister Mary Kenneth Keller', 'Evelyn Boyd Granville', 'Kay McNulty']
	},
	{
		question: 'The first woman in the United States to ever earn her Ph.D. in Computer Science was:',
		answer: 'Sister Mary Kenneth Keller',
		choices: ['Edith Clarke', 'Sister Mary Kenneth Keller', 'Carol Shaw', 'Anita Borg']
	},
	{
		question: 'A highly respected computer scientist who advocated for equal representation of women in computer science. In 1987, she created Systers, an email list community exclusively for women in computing.',
		answer: 'Anita Borg',
		choices: ['Jean Bartik', 'Anita Borg', 'Hedy Lamarr', 'Sister Mary Kenneth Keller',]
	},
	{
		question: 'After ending a career as an actress for MGM, she went on to develop a system that inspired the technology that is now used to maintain the security of cell phones and military communications',
		answer: 'Hedy Lamarr',
		choices: ['Betty Holberton', 'Kay McNulty', 'Hedy Lamarr', 'Edie Windsor',]
	},
	{
		question: 'This woman was an American computer scientist and United States Navy rear admiral who invented one of the first compiler related tools',
		answer: 'Grace Hopper',
		choices: ['Kay McNulty', 'Grace Hopper', 'Evelyn Boyd Granville', 'Hedy Lamarr']
	},
	{
		question: 'Which woman was one of the first female IBM managers and an LGBT equality activist?',
		answer: 'Edie Windsor',
		choices: ['Edith Clarke', 'Jean Bartik', 'Edie Windsor', 'Betty Holberton']
	},
	{
		question: 'Considered by many to be the first female video game designer, she developed games at Atari, Tandem Computers and Activision for the Atari 2600, including "3-D Tic-Tac-Toe" and "Video Checkers."',
		answer: 'Carol Shaw',
		choices: ['Ada Lovelace', 'Hedy Lamarr', 'Grace Hopper', 'Carol Shaw']
	},
	{
		question: 'One of the six original programmers of ENIAC, the first general-purpose electronic digital computer, and the inventor of breakpoints in computer debugging.',
		answer: 'Betty Holberton',
		choices: ['Betty Holberton', 'Evelyn Boyd Granville', 'Sister Mary Kenneth Keller', 'Edie Windsor']
	},
	{
		question: 'She was the first female electrical engineer and the first woman to ever earn an M.S. in Electrical Engineering from MIT.',
		answer: 'Edith Clarke',
		choices: ['Betty Holberton', 'Edie Windsor', 'Evelyn Boyd Granville', 'Edith Clarke']
	},
	{
		question: 'One of the first people to ever realize that machines had potential far beyond simple computations, she is considered by many to be the first computer programmer.',
		answer: 'Ada Lovelace',
		choices: ['Ada Lovelace', 'Sister Mary Kenneth Keller', 'Kay McNulty', 'Jean Bartik']
	}
];